const questions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "A relation R from A to B is defined by R = {(1, 5), (2, 6), (3, 7)}. Then the domain and range of R are respectively:",
      options: {
        a: "D = {1, 2, 3}, R = {5, 6, 7}",
        b: "D = {5, 6, 7}, R = {1, 2, 3}",
        c: "D = {1, 6, 7}, R = {5, 2, 3}",
        d: "D = R = {5, 6, 7}"
      },
      answer: "a"
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "If a tanθ = b, then the value of a cos²θ + b sin²θ is:",
      options: {
        a: "a² + b²",
        b: "a",
        c: "b",
        d: "2b"
      },
      answer: "a"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "If a, b, c are in G.P. and a^(1/x) = b^(1/y) = c^(1/z), then x, y, z are in:",
      options: {
        a: "A.P.",
        b: "G.P.",
        c: "H.P.",
        d: "None"
      },
      answer: "c"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "If A + B = [[1, 1], [0, 1]] and A – 2B = [[-1, 0], [1, -1]], then A is:",
      options: {
        a: "[[1, 2], [1, 1]]",
        b: "[[2/3, 1/3], [1/3, 2/3]]",
        c: "[[1/3, 2/3], [1/3, 1/3]]",
        d: "[[1, 0], [0, 1]]"
      },
      answer: "a"
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "lim (x → 0) [(5^x + 3^x – 2^x)] is:",
      options: {
        a: "loge5 – loge3",
        b: "log5log3",
        c: "5/3 log2",
        d: "loge(3 × 5)"
      },
      answer: "d"
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "The function f(x) = 1/(1 - x) is:",
      options: {
        a: "continuous and derivable at x = 1",
        b: "neither continuous nor derivable at x = 1",
        c: "continuous but not derivable at x = 0",
        d: "derivable but not continuous at x = 0"
      },
      answer: "b"
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "∫ (e^(2x) - 1)/(e^x + 1) dx is:",
      options: {
        a: "e^(2x)/2 - e^x + c",
        b: "e^x - x + c",
        c: "e^(x/2) + x + c",
        d: "(e^x - 1)²/2 + c"
      },
      answer: "a"
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "(a⁶ - b⁶) × (a⁶ + b⁶) is equal to:",
      options: {
        a: "0",
        b: "a⁶ × b⁶",
        c: "2(a⁶ × b⁶)",
        d: "|a⁶|² - |b⁶|²"
      },
      answer: "d"
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "The locus of the point which is equidistant from the x-axis and y-axis is:",
      options: {
        a: "y = 2x",
        b: "3x - y = 0",
        c: "x - y = 0",
        d: "x + 4y = 0"
      },
      answer: "c"
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "The equation xy = 0 in three-dimensional space represents:",
      options: {
        a: "a pair of straight lines",
        b: "a plane",
        c: "a pair of planes at right angles",
        d: "a pair of parallel lines"
      },
      answer: "c"
    }
  ];
  
  export default questions;
  